

Md Samim Akhter

Search Engine Evaluator

mdsamimakhter2001@gmail.com

+919635322864

Abinashpur, Birbhum

linkedin.com/in/md-samim-akhter in

facebook.com/imdsamimakhter

imdsamimakhter.github.io/portfolio

Hello, Myself Md Samim Akhter, a 22-year-old individual with in-depth knowledge of Search Engine, is a highly motivated and skilled person. I'm passionate about social justice and making a positive impact in the society, and I'm excited to see what the future holds.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Search Engine Evaluator (Part-Time)

Welocalize.inc

AI Content Rewriter (Freelance)

Google Bard

Al Writing & Examine

UHRS Surfer (Freelance)

Telus International.inc

CrowdSourcing and Data Annotation Expert

Blogging

Google Blogger

2020 - 2022

Customer Service

Rinku Electronics

2017 - 2022

Resolving queries regarding products and services

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Science and Technology

Santiniketan Institute of Polytechnic

08/2020 - 07/2023

Muluk, Birbhum

Bachelor of Arts (BA)

Birbhum Mahavidyalaya

08/2020 - 07/2023

Suri , Birbhum

Senior Secondary Education (10th+2)

Abinashpur High School

05/2018 - 03/2020 Abinashpur, Birbhum

Secondary Education (10th)

Abinashpur High School

01/2016 - 01/2020 Abinashpur, Birbhum

SKILLS

HTML SQL Google Workplace

MS 365 Transcription

MS Word & MS Excel Email Marketing

Data Migration Communication

Social Interection Translation

CERTIFICATES

Negotiation

Machine Learning & Data Science with Python-Intership (03/2023 - 06/2023)

C & Python

PHN Technology Pvt. Ltd.

IT/ITES (NSDC) NSQF L.v-4 (01/2016 - 12/2019)

Abinashpur High School

Diploma in Information Technology Application (DITA) (04/2018 - 04/2019)

Panrui Youth Computer Training Centre

Tally ERP 9 Training (04/2019 - 10/2019)

Panrui Youth Computer Training Centre

LANGUAGES

English Bengali
Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual
Proficiency

Hind

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Cycling, Painting, Listening Stories, Playing Football, Volley, Puzzle Solving, Online Games and many more.